[
  {
    "answer": "Alef",
    "question": "א"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bet",
    "question": "ב‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gimel",
    "question": "ג‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dalet",
    "question": "ד‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He",
    "question": "ה‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vav",
    "question": "ו‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zayin",
    "question": "ז‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Het",
    "question": "ח‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tet",
    "question": "ט"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yod",
    "question": "י"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kaf",
    "question": "כך‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lamed",
    "question": "ל‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mem",
    "question": "מ‬ם"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Nun",
    "question": "נ‬ן‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Samekh",
    "question": "ס"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ayin",
    "question": "ע‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pe",
    "question": "פ‬ף"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tsadi",
    "question": "צ‬ץ‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Qof",
    "question": "ק‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Resh",
    "question": "ר‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sin",
    "question": "ש‬"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tav",
    "question": "ת‬"
  }
]
